<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>leader on robinbb</title>
    <link>https://robinbb.com/tags/leader/</link>
    <description>Recent content in leader on robinbb</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://robinbb.com/tags/leader/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Robin Bate Boerop</title>
      <link>https://robinbb.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robinbb.com/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet With Robin</title>
      <link>https://robinbb.com/meet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robinbb.com/meet/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Results</title>
      <link>https://robinbb.com/results/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robinbb.com/results/</guid>
      <description>Software Teams Improved I am a hands-on leadership consultant for deep-tech software teams.
Here are the results that I get:
 Deployable software Reduced employee turnover Better team decision-making De-risked technology strategies Tuned agile development processes World-class build automation software Increased confidence in deployed software Reduced recruiting costs by effective hiring Measurable increase of development velocity Measurable improvement of employee engagement Software architecture recommendations worth implementing Substantial productivity improvements that last  To learn more about my leadership style and philosophy, watch my videos on Twitter or LinkedIn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robin Bate Boerop</title>
      <link>https://robinbb.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robinbb.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Global Software Leadership Consultant I make winning software teams by providing hands-on engineering leadership.
I have developed software professionally for 20 years. I have led software teams in consulting engagements and as part of Silicon Valley tech startups. I co-founded a Canadian software startup that was acquired in 2014.
I advise for Tweag.
Results Meet      Speaking engagements Results Schedule a meeting Press citation Startup acquisition My c.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talk - Software Testing: Stories From The Real World</title>
      <link>https://robinbb.com/talk-nbq-2016-oct-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robinbb.com/talk-nbq-2016-oct-4/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday, 4 October 2016
Software Testing Env  What organization culture gives rise to the testing and software development process? What is the testing and software development process? What problems are exhibited by that process?  5 different testing experiences  University coding project Tech startup company (web app) Enterprise software consulting project (2) Prominent open source software (Mozilla) Database software (IBM)  Career Tips  RobinBB software valuation method. Know and satisfy your client.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
